like, all right,
there are only
so many hours
in the day,
and your community
probably has a
nearly unlimited demand
to interact with
you, and you
want to interact
with them because
you're trying to
grow your community.
Both socially
and from a business
perspective, that's
sort of growing
the community is
an important part
of what every
creator does. So,
okay, if we
can make it
so that each
creator can
basically make an
AI artifact that
their community can
interact with, people
will be clear-
that it's not
the actual creator
themselves, but it's
almost like a
piece of digital
art that you're
producing, like an
interactive sculpture or
something that it's
like you train
it to, here's
the context that
I want it
to have.
Here's the topics
I want it
to communicate on.
Here's stuff that
I want it
to stay away
from. You're giving
your community something
to interact with
when you can't
be there to
kind of answer
all the questions.